{
  "type": "quiz",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "が",
      "answer": "ga"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぎ",
      "answer": "gi"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぐ",
      "answer": "gu"
    },
    {
      "question": "げ",
      "answer": "ge"
    },
    {
      "question": "ご",
      "answer": "go"
    },
    {
      "question": "ざ",
      "answer": "za"
    },
    {
      "question": "じ",
      "answer": "ji"
    },
    {
      "question": "ず",
      "answer": "zu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぜ",
      "answer": "ze"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぞ",
      "answer": "zo"
    },
    {
      "question": "だ",
      "answer": "da"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぢ",
      "answer": "ji"
    },
    {
      "question": "づ",
      "answer": "zu"
    },
    {
      "question": "で",
      "answer": "de"
    },
    {
      "question": "ど",
      "answer": "do"
    },
    {
      "question": "ば",
      "answer": "ba"
    },
    {
      "question": "び",
      "answer": "bi"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぶ",
      "answer": "bu"
    },
    {
      "question": "べ",
      "answer": "be"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぼ",
      "answer": "bo"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぱ",
      "answer": "pa"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぴ",
      "answer": "pi"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぷ",
      "answer": "pu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぺ",
      "answer": "pe"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぽ",
      "answer": "po"
    }
  ]
}
